Today we will talk about SSC number.
First I had to see the disclaimer.
Whatever stock comment I am making is only
for additional purpose. What is its distance? If you have done
business with it, you should do it at this
point. Not any financial
advisor on motor spirit advisor.
So our main basic topic today is SSC
Lamba General Insurance Company which
is an insurance company and this is now the
customer subsidiary of ICC. Lamba and this general
insurance company has two. Now let's talk about its
values. Its market cap
is more than that of that Chhachh Exam and it is 611
subscribers. It is a debit free company. The
debt is not much, there is a decrease of 425 crores.
Its market cap is the lowest
hands free cash.
Yes, so now let's see for the basics.
Now let's see on spinner. What is that
Saver Mod. Before the 200th test
match, 1451 officers have a difference of ₹1. It is a
very good thing. There are
highs on its volumes. So on the contrary, its
pros and cons of  It is almost a free company, for the
first time I am fat in these 32.75 serial
returns, Care Love Affair dividend
payout is 70% very turmeric spread, stock
trading is from the book value, hi hand
computers pairs,
behind this from now on life insurance
ICICI Lombard itself from its two sides,
like in Corona time also
entries were made from its sale and from Corona screen
from December 2018, so it kept increasing
and who is that the actress is emphasizing
that all the remaining increasing thickness I can see,
from 1111 phase 11th 12th to 1000, it seems better, there are
some changes on share capitals, on the contrary, some people are
coming in increase in cash deposits and it is as good as it is
and then promoter holding on gas,
promoter holding is a bit more, now there are
no changes, just Sachin, whom we if it is a
good thing that in F-18, he is continuously increasing his status,
2% above director, one was appointed chairman and now
Subscribe and increase them a little in the box, they have gone up by
14%.
Yes, now let's talk about its chart. So,
here in the chart, currently the
office, as I said, is
trading on medium level. Will see a little
till 420. That person gets equal
rights. So subscribe, salute
for them. Again, it is tested very well.
Subscribe, subscribe and subscribe.
It will increase with pump volume. Now let's
see what is its result. The
reason for the decline is that
ICICI Bank, which is its subordinate
bank, has reduced its withdrawal acid number. Subscribe to this channel
and let's talk about the target.
So subscribe to our channel.
Jeevan More Subscribe
2012 and the quality timeline will remain.
Subscribe to school
AP. If we see here, yes, I am
seeing this in the one day chart and the
person who was here, this thing that is war,
come here, so this is Ballu, you get relief. Yes,
this Punarnava. Yes, so very quickly, ask
me for this.